export const data = [
    {
        question:"What is perimeter of circle ?",
        option1: "πr",
        option2:"2πr",
        option3:"2π+r",
        option4:"2πr^2",
        ans:2,

    },
    {
        question:"What is area of circle ?",
        option1: "πr*r",
        option2:"2πr",
        option3:"2π+r",
        option4:"2πr*r",
        ans:1,

    },
    {
        question:"What is circumference of circle ?",
        option1: "πr",
        option2:"2πr",
        option3:"πr*r",
        option4:"2πr*r",
        ans:2,

    },
    {
        question:" The area of a rhombus whose diagonals are of lengths 5 cm and 4.2 cm is:",
        option1: " 41 cm2",
        option2:" 14.5cm2",
        option3:"10.5cm2",
        option4:"20.5cm2",
        ans:3,

    },
   
    {
        question:"The perimeter of a rectangle with length (l) and width (w) is:",
        option1: "l+w",
        option2:"2(l+w)",
        option3:"(l+w)2",
        option4:" lw",
        ans:2,

    },
    {
        question:"What is area of Rectangle ?",
        option1: "ab",
        option2:"2ab",
        option3:"2(a+b)",
        option4:"2a+2",
        ans:1,

    },
    {
        question:"Area of the square with side-length ‘a’ is:",
        option1: " a2",
        option2:" 2a",
        option3:" 4a",
        option4:" a/2",
        ans:1,

    },
    {
        question:"The area of a parallelogram with length (l) and breadth (b) is:",
        option1: " ½ lb",
        option2:" 2lb",
        option3:" lb",
        option4:" (lb)2",
        ans:3,

    },
    {
        question:"Volume of a cylinder with base radius = r and height = h, is:",
        option1: " 2πrh",
        option2:"  πr²h",
        option3:"  2πr (r + h)",
        option4:"  1/3 πr²h",
        ans:2,

    },
    {
        question:" Volume of a cuboid of length (l), width (w) and height (h) is:",
        option1: " lbh",
        option2:" lb + bh + hl",
        option3:"2 (lb + bh + hl)",
        option4:"2 (l + b) h",
        ans:1,

    },
    {
        question:" Surface area of cube of edge ‘a’ is:",
        option1: "4a²",
        option2:" 6a²",
        option3:" 3a²",
        option4:" a²",
        ans:2,

    },
    {
        question:" Area of a triangle with base (b) and height (h) is:",
        option1: "b.h",
        option2:" ½ b.h",
        option3:"2b.h",
        option4:"None of these",
        ans:2,

    },
    
    
   
];

